Caleb Hebert

□ caleb.b.hebert@outlook.com | (808) 798-6486 |

 □ San Antonio, TX

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/calebhebert | https://github.com/ctrl-alt-caleb

Professional Summary

Air Force Veteran completing four years of honorable service with an active TS/SCI security clearance with 4 years of experience in server and systems administration.

Skills

C#	Active Directory	Server Administration
JavaScript	Azure	Vulnerability Patching
HTML/CSS	MS SQL Server	Model View Controller (MVC)
Professional Experience	c e	
•		
<u> </u>	Microsoft Software and Systems A	cademy, Microsoft
 07/2022 – 11/2022	Microsoft Software and Systems A	cademy, Microsoft with C# for object-oriented programming,
<u> </u>	Microsoft Software and Systems A • Employed the .NET framework	with C# for object-oriented programming, ning, performance and memory management,
<u> </u>	 Microsoft Software and Systems A Employed the .NET framework debugging tools, I/O programn database access and data encr 	with C# for object-oriented programming, ning, performance and memory management,

04/2018 – 07/2022

Virtual Desktop Infrastructure Engineer, United States Air Force

- Planned and coordinated installation, testing, operations, patching, troubleshooting, and maintenance of Windows and Linux based hardware and software servers and client systems
- Implemented PowerShell script to reduce vulnerability patching time by 70%
- Managed VDI environment; configured VMware vSphere, VMware Horizon, and SecureView systems supporting over 15,000 personnel across 9 bases
- Performed vulnerability management on critical joint planning software;
 eliminated hundreds of vulnerabilities including DOD's #1 cyber vulnerability
 across 4 bases on 24 virtual servers
 - Air Force Achievement Medal (2x), United States Air Force
 - Action Officer of the Quarter, United States Air Force
 - Airman of the Quarter, United States Air Force

Education

08/2019 – present

Computer Science B.S, *Hawaii Pacific University* (90 credit hours completed)

 Coursework: Computer Programming; Databases; Algorithms; Operating Systems; Statistics; Calculus I & II

Certifications

2022	IT Specialist – Software Development
2018	CompTIA Security+